{
    "subject": "resource/Warner_Baxter",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Beverly_Hills,_California",
    "human_readable": "Warner Baxter died in Beverly Hills, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8873562216758728,
            "question": "Where did Warner Baxter die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.778580367565155,
            "question": "What state was Warner Baxter living in when he died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6599423289299011,
            "question": "In which city is Warner Baxter buried?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42668211460113525,
            "question": "Was Warner Baxter an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35602232813835144,
            "question": "What other information do you know about Warner Baxter's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3281639516353607,
            "question": "During what period was Warner Baxter active in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27872878313064575,
            "question": "What was Warner Baxter's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27688801288604736,
            "question": "Was Warner Baxter known for any particular roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26454877853393555,
            "question": "Are there any notable films starring Warner Baxter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21381868422031403,
            "question": "Did Warner Baxter win any awards during his career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warner Baxter died in Beverly Hills, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7194_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable films starring Warner Baxter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7194_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Warner Baxter known for any particular roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7194_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Warner Baxter's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7194_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7194_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Multiple documents confirm that Warner Baxter's place of death was indeed Beverly Hills, California."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Warner Baxter died in Beverly Hills, California.\" Specifically, document `15.txt` states his location of death as \"Beverly Hills, CA\", which aligns with the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}